SHAMYATA BISWAL

SUMMARY

5 years of experience in hospitality industry in aviation and business event planning. Worked with SpiceJet as a cabin crew both for international and national flights. Handled multiple successful campaigns for Punjab Television network, Toyota, Godrej and many other clients.

CONTACT

□ shamyata.biswal89@gmail.com

□ 9899265377

Skype Id: live:bc5be18cf533f5d9

EDUCATION

Guru Jambheshwar University PG Mass Communication 2016

Madhu Bala Institute of Communication and Electronic Media

Bachelors Journalism and Mass Communication 2013

South Delhi, Polytechnic Diploma Mass Communication 2010

SKILLS

PREOFESSIONAL: Persuasive communicator,

Grooming and self-presentation,

Effective communication,

Excellent listening and understanding abilities,

Delivering customer service and customer experience,

creative plans and innovative strategies,

Proactive and ability to handle emergency, Trained in

Aviation emergency equipment **TECHNICAL:** MS

Office, Adobe Photoshop

AWARDS

Spicejet · Best Grooming Award

Oct. 2016

Spicejet · Best Employee

2016

Thrice awarded as best employee for achieving above target sales in flights.

INTERESTS

EMPLOYMENT

Spicejet Ahmedabad

Cabin Crew Member · 2016 to 2018

Responsible to provide excellent customer service to passengers ensuring their comfort and safety throughout the flight

Trained to deal with security, any kind of emergency situation , providing first aid

Served in 700/800 /900 Boeing international and national flights

Supervised cabin crew team independently during flights

Aurra Entertaintment Delhi

Creative Assistant · Oct. 2014 to 2016

Key Responsibilities were planning of concepts for events, client handling, liaison between client and our operational team

Worked with Punjab Television Network as an Assistant Director and was responsible for styling part of a program named "LAUGHTER THE MASTER"

Blazewell Events Delhi

Executive-CS & PR · Feb. 2014 to Oct. 2014

Key Responsibilities were planning of concepts for events, client handling, liaison between client and company operational team, lead generation, working on prospective customers in terms of regular follow up for their upcoming events.

Successfully got and handled Godrej and Geojit BNP Paribas on board with Blazewell Events

Auraa Entertainments Delhi

Creative Assistant · 2013 to 2014

Key Responsibilities were planning of concepts for events, client Handling and liaison between client and our operational team

Navbharat Times and UFI Productions Intern

Worked on Articles, Corporate Movies and Script Writing